Guide to the Libraries Reference collection, 1972-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Libraries Reference collection 1972-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.7 Linear Feet 700 Items
The Libraries Reference Collection contains files of clippings, memoranda, publications, reports, statistics and other material about the Duke University libraries, their history, administration, staffing, policies, and collections.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
This collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
Collection Overview
The Libraries Reference Collection contains files of clippings, memoranda, publications, reports, statistics and other material about the Duke University libraries, their history, administration, staffing, policies, and collections. This collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Library -- History
Triangle Research Libraries Network
Related Material
Duke University Libraries. Records, 1892-
Duke University Archives
Detailed Description of Collection
- Container List
  - Administration
  - Anniversaries, 2, 3, &4 Millionth volume
  - Automation
  - Brochures, 1963, [1972]
  - Clippings
  - Collections
    - Barchas, 1974-1975
    - Kanof, 1991
    - Mazzoni, undated
  - Departments (Perkins)
  - Events and exhibits, undated
  - Faculty Survey Committee Report, 1983
  - Friends of the Duke University Library, circa 1970
  - Guides and handbooks, 1931-
  - Handbook for Bi-Wekly Employees, 1972-
  - The Henkel Press, 1931-
  - History
  - Libraries
    - Biological and Environmental Sciences
    - Lilly
    - Professional schools
    - David M. Rubenstein Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Duke University
      - General, 1997
      - Jay B. Hubbell Center, 1981-1982
      - John Hope Franklin Center, 1995-
      - John W. Hartman Center, 1995-
      - Sallie Bingham Center, 2000-
    - Vesic, 2000
  - Library cooperation, 1935-
  - Living History Program, circa 1979-
  - Perkins Library System: The Staff in Pictures, [1989]
  - Policies, 1972-
  - Staff news, 1995-
  - Statistics, 1934-
  - Triangle Research Libraries Network (TRLN), 1986-
  - University Archives, 1960-